Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Solidarity is the banner, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. International Affairs Department.
  - Item 4: The world as we see it: 4 resolutions on international labor solidarity ..., 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Trade union problems: the Middle East, 1962; Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
    Author: Arnold Beichman
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Walter Reuther's great big union, 1963; Publication (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: A picture history of the UAW-CIO, 1945; Publication (Box 90, Folder 9)
    Notes: UAW-CIO Ammunition, vol.11:no.3. 2 copies
  - Item 3: ILR 110, Graduate Seminar in the history and government of labor unions, Sept. 1948 to Feb. 1949, 1948-1949 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: In the great tradition, 11th Convention, UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 90, Folder 9)
    Notes: Conference booklet. Copy 2
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A brief history of the UAW, Publication (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: UAW Solidarity, 1977; Publication (Box 90, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.20:no.7 (1977:May 13)
  - Item 3: The UAW: its heritage and history, 1974; Publication (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Labor's historic support of public education: a chronology, 1974; Publication (Box 90, Folder 10)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: News letter, International Harvester Dept., UAW-AFL-CIO, 1956; Publication (Box 90, Folder 11)
    Notes: Jan., Apr. 1956
  - Item 2: News letter, International Harvester Dept., UAW-AFL-CIO, 1959; Publication (Box 90, Folder 11)
    Notes: Feb. 1959
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor great books program, 1950; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan., Apr. 1950
  - Item 2: Labor great books program, 1951; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: June, July, Oct., Dec. 1951
  - Item 3: Labor great books program, 1952; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: \Jan., May 1952
  - Item 4: Who gets how much?, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Wife in step, Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Correspondence to Mr. Walter P. Reuther from United States Senate - March 23, 1957, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Problems of regional and industrial unemployment, 1955; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Statement of UAW President Walter P. Reuther, to the House Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Wednesday, May 11, 1966, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Testimony of UAW Education Director Carroll Hutton, prepared for presentation to the House Education and Labor Committee Select Committee on Education, April 13, 1961, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Author: Carroll Hutton
  - Item 5: Testimony of Walter P. Reuther, President, Congress of Industrial Organizations, on Automation, before the Sub-Committee on Economic Stabilization of the Joint Committee on the Economic Report, October 17, 1955, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Text of letter to all members of the United States Senate and House of Representatives, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Text of the letter, to Senator Estes Kefauver., 1957; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Administered prices in the automobile industry, 1958; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Price policy and public responsibility; administered prices in the automobile industry, 1958; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Proposal to limit campaign contributions, submitted to Congress, July 1956, Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Voting record of the 94th Congress, 1976; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A brief history of the labor movement of Studebaker, 1953; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (CIO). Studebaker Local No. 5.
  - Item 2: Copy of a letter received from R.A. Vail, vice-President, in charge of Production in regard to piece work rate adjustments) - June 20, 1946, Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A guide to the preparation of by-laws for local unions of the UAW-CIO ..., 1944; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: A guide to the preparation of by-laws for local unions of the UAW-CIO ..., 1946; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: You and the draft; what you should know about it: deferments, classification, appeals, financial relief., 1941; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Annual report to membership, 1952, Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 6 (Melrose Park, Ill.)
  - Item 2: The Union Voice, 1953; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: Oct.2,9,16,23; Nov.6,13,20,25 (1953)
  - Item 3: The Union Voice, 1954; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jan.8,15,22,29; Feb.5; Sept.17 (1954)
  - Item 4: UAW-CIO International Harvester Council - Correspondence, 1954; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 57 News Letter, 1955; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.1:no.2-3,7,9-11
  - Item 2: 57 News Letter, 1956; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-5-6,8-9,11-16,18- 23
  - Item 3: 57 News Letter, 1957; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.3:no.2-3,6, 10,13,17 (1957)
  - Item 4: 57 News Letter, 1959; Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.4:no.2,5,7 (1959)
  - Item 5: News letter - Feb. 1956, Publication (Box 91, Folder 6)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Pencil Pusher, UAW Office Workers Union, Local 305, Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.2:no.7 (April)
  - Item 2: Pencil Pusher, UAW Office Workers Union, Local 305, Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.3:no.3 (April)
  - Item 3: Time Study, Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Manual for stewards and committeemen, Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 212 (Detroit, Mich.)
  - Item 5: Steward's and Committeeman's manual, Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Your local union in Action, West Side Local 174, U.A.W.-C.I.O.: Building today for a better tomorrow, Publication (Box 91, Folder 7)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 174 (Detroit, Mich.)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 501 Organizer, 1947; Publication (Box 91, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.3:no.3-8 (1947)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Who is un-American at Bell Aircraft?, 1949; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: The Story of the Bell strike, 1949; Publication (Box 91, Folder 9)
    Author: Edward F. Gray
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Story of the Bell strike, 1949; Publication (Box 91, Folder 10)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The home of the Ford Roge Employees Federal Credit Union - advertisement flyer, Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: UAW Local 600 Strike at Ford Motor Company, May 1949, Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 770's UAW-CIO News, 1951; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1- 10
  - Item 2: 770's UAW-CIO News, 1952; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-8
  - Item 3: 770's UAW-CIO News, 1953; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.3:no.1-3
  - Item 4: 770's UAW-CIO News, 1954; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1
  - Item 5: 770's UAW-CIO News, 1955; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: Strike edition
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, UAW Local 833, 1959; Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.2:no.349, Friday, Mar. 13, 1959
  - Item 2: Can America afford Kohlerism, a return to the 1930's, 1957; Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Congressional Record, Proceedings and Debates of the 85th Congress, first session, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Don't buy Kohler, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Facts and figures in connection with UAW Local 833 and the Kohler Strike, 1957; Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: How Frank Novak fell victim to 'Kohler Disease', Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Author: Karl Kotnick
  - Item 7: How to boycott Kohler, report for the membership of your union, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: How you can stop union busting, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Kohler Co. found guilty of prolonging strike, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Kohlerism can be defeated, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Silicosis, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: The Journal of plumbing, heating & air conditioning, 1956; Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Notes: (Oct. 1956)
  - Item 13: The Kohler Strike Hearings, prepared statements, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: The Kohler strikers and their friends present the Local 833 Chorus, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: The Kohlerian, 1955; Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.18:no.20 (1955)
  - Item 16: please help my daddy win the Kohler Strike, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Bathtub Baron, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Notes: Article from June, 1954, issue of Ammunition. Copy 2
  - Item 18: Boycott Fillers #10, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Bulletin, UAW Local 833, 1958; Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.2:no.338, Friday, Dec. 12, 1958
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: a summary of the NLRB decision on Kohler Strike issued by UAW Secretary-Treasurer Emil Mazey, Sept. 2, 1960, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Antidote of facts, figures, and issues, 1960; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1 (1960)
  - Item 3: Autoworkers will be heard! to Leonard Woodcock, International Union, and UAW Convention Delegates, from - Rank and File UAW Members in Northern California, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: BNA's daily reporter system, Daily Labor Report, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.243
  - Item 5: Kohler in non-compliance with NLRB order, claim, 1961; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: Oversize copy of an article from The Sheboggan Press, Thursday, April 20, 1961
  - Item 6: Kohler of Kohler News, 1955; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1955 April
  - Item 7: Local 1097 UAW - Pre-Retirement Planning, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Local 604's Reporter, 1947; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.1:no.2-6,8 (1947)
  - Item 9: Minutes of meeting on training of union counselors, 1944; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Pension Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: Flyer from Chase Brass & Copper Co.
  - Item 11: Proceedings of Special Session, International Executive Board, UAW, Region 2B, Local 549, Show Cause Hearing, Wednesday, March 8, 1967, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Verdict at Kohler, by Rev. Charles Owen Rice, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Author: Charles Owen Rice
  - Item 13: White Collar News, 1950; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Build labor party: fight reaction, 1947; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Chase Brass and Copper Company, 1954; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: correspondence - from UAW to "Local 833 Member", 1960; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: correspondence - from UAW to "The Kohler Company", Sept. 1, 1960, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: The story of Dodge Local No. 3 UAW-CIO, 1941; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: They're on the march: against the people, 1943; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Local 12 UAW-AFL-CIO, Summer Camp, 1957; Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Local 142, UAW-CIO, Union information for new employees, Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Program for retired workers centers from August 6 to September 7, 1956, Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Your membership with Local 212, Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Are war plants expendable?, 1945; Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Winning the battle for production, Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Author: Curt Murdock
  - Item 7: Your local union in Action, West Side Local 174, U.A.W.-C.I.O.: Building today for a better tomorrow, Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 248 Reporter, 1957; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.10:no.3 (1957)
  - Item 2: Aircraft Reminder, 1953; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-2 (1953:Mar.)
  - Item 3: An Initiation Ceremony, Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Notes: Meeting agenda
  - Item 4: CIO Memorial Building, Local 686, UAW-CIO, Souvenir Program, 1946; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Dedicated to Service, Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Notes: Booklet of service honorees
  - Item 6: Dodge Local 3, UAW-CIO, Educational Yearbook, 1946 -, Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Fired, 14 Centuries of Labor, Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Flint Weekly Review, 1959; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Notes: Thurs., Oct. 15, 1959
  - Item 9: Local #566 News, UAW-CIO, 1953; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Notes: (Dec. 1953)
  - Item 10: Rochester-Product's, Voice of Labor, Publication of Local 1097, UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: The Conveyor, 1947; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.2:no.2 (1947:Jan.)
  - Item 12: Training Program, Local 501, UAW-CIO, 1952; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: The Next five years: a story of the contract between Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company and Local 248 United Auto Workers-CIO., 1950; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 501 Organizer, 1954; Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Notes: 1954 March 11
  - Item 2: Local 566 News, 1953; Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Notes: Sept 7 & 23, 1953, Nov. 25, 1953, Dec. 1953,
  - Item 3: Local 810 News, UAW-CIO, 1953; Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1 (1953)
  - Item 4: The Breakwall-News, 1946; Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.1:no.9 (1946)
  - Item 5: The Breakwall-News, 1947; Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1 (1947)
  - Item 6: UAW Lubricator, CIO, Green Sheet, 1948; Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Notes: 1948 July
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Medical Research Institute UAW-CIO, 1943; Publication (Box 92, Folder 8)
    Notes: 1943 Convention, Buffalo, NY
  - Item 2: Report of National Citizens Committee on GM-UAW-CIO Dispute, Detroit, Michigan, 1945; Publication (Box 92, Folder 8)
    Notes: 1945 December
  - Item 3: UAW-CIO Washington, News Flash, 1944; Publication (Box 92, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.2:no.7, 13 (1944)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: News from the UAW-CIO, 1951; Publication (Box 93, Folder 1)
    Notes: Oct. 7, 15, 1951
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: News from the UAW-CIO - Sixth UAW-CIO Int'l. Educ. Conf., Opening Address by Pres. Walter Reuther, 1954; Publication (Box 93, Folder 2)
    Notes: June-Nov. 1954
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 2,500 UAW Delegates to meet in Chicago at Union's Biennial Education Conference, 1954; Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Civil rights for minorities, 1954; Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Hungry people and surplus food, 1954; Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Issues of the 1954 Congressional Election, Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: News from the UAW-CIO, 1953; Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
    Notes: Nov. 1953-Dec. 1953
  - Item 6: News from the UAW-CIO, 1954; Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan.-May 1954
  - Item 7: Paul Hoffman, Studebaker Board Chairman to speak at UAW Education Conference, 1954; Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
    Author: Paul Hoffman
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: News from the UAW-CIO, 1953; Publication (Box 93, Folder 4)
    Notes: Nov.-Dec. 1953
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: News from the UAW-CIO, 1955-1956 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jan, July-Dec. 1955, Jan. 1956
  - Item 2: News from the UAW-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 93, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jan.-July 1955
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: correspondence - to "All UAW-CIO Local Union Presidents, Recording Secretaries, Chairmen and Members of Local Union Fair Practices Committees - All Regions", 1955; Publication (Box 93, Folder 6)
    Notes: Regarding civil rights - Emmett Louis Till - (14 year old lynched on Aug. 29, 1955 & October 27
  - Item 2: December 21, 1955 - regarding a pension plan contained in the agreement between Chrysler and the UAW, Publication (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: UAW-CIO Public Relations Dept. regarding a new agreement with the Ford Motor Company Sept. 4, 1950, Publication (Box 93, Folder 6)
    Author: UAW-CIO Public Relations Dept.
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Biographical sketch of Walter P. Reuther, President, Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: News from the UAW-CIO, 1956; Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan-Apr, Aug-Dec 1956
  - Item 3: Resolution condemning Soviet brutality and pledging support and solidarity to the people of Hungary, Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Supplementary unemployment benefit plans and unemployment compensation amendments by Nat Weinberg, 1956; Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Letter to 'The Honorable Dwight D. Eisenhower' - regarding inflation, 1956; Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: News from the UAW-CIO, 1956; Publication (Box 93, Folder 8)
    Notes: Apr-Oct 1956
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Press Releases from UAW, 1958; Publication (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.-Mar. 1958
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Press Release - "When Mr. Mazey appears before the Senate Select Committee", 1958; Publication (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Press Releases from UAW, 1958; Publication (Box 94, Folder 2)
    Notes: Apr.-June 1958
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Press Releases from UAW, 1958; Publication (Box 94, Folder 3)
    Notes: July-Sept. 1958
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Press Releases from UAW, 1958; Publication (Box 94, Folder 4)
    Notes: Oct.-Dec. 1958
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Press Releases from UAW, 1959; Publication (Box 94, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jan.-May, Oct.-Nov. 1959
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Press Releases from UAW, 1960; Publication (Box 95, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.-Dec. 1960
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Press Releases from UAW, 1961; Publication (Box 95, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan., Mar.-Dec. 1961
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Press Releases from UAW, 1962; Publication (Box 95, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan.-Dec. 1962
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Press Releases from UAW, 1963; Publication (Box 95, Folder 4)
    Notes: Jan.-Sept., Nov.-Dec. 1963
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: News from UAW, 1964; Publication (Box 95, Folder 5)